Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Ah!
اه!
Innkeeper, hurry!
صاحب النزل، بسرعة!
Saving lives is more important!
إنقاذ الأرواح هو الأهم!
Dongfang!
دونغفانغ!
Innkeeper,
صاحب النزل،
what happened?
ماذا حدث؟
I promised
لقد وعدت
to protect your life.
لحماية حياتك.
Innkeeper,
صاحب النزل،
we can't make the same mistake again.
لا يمكننا أن نرتكب نفس الخطأ مرة أخرى.
Hey!
يا!
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
Alright.
على ما يرام.
The troupe master is dead!
لقد مات رئيس الفرقة!
Someone's been killed!
لقد تم قتل شخص ما!
There's been a murder!
لقد حدثت جريمة قتل!
Hurry!
عجل!
It's him!
إنه هو!
It's Mei Jiulang
إنها مي جيولانغ
who killed our Imperial Uncle.
من قتل عمنا الإمبراطوري؟
What?
ماذا؟
The Imperial Uncle is dead?
هل العم الإمبراطوري مات؟
How is that possible?
كيف ذلك ممكنا؟
Mei Jiulang,
مي جيولانج,
someone has accused you
لقد اتهمك شخص ما
of going to the Imperial Uncle's mansion by invitation last night
من الذهاب إلى قصر العم الإمبراطوري بدعوة الليلة الماضية
and killing the old Imperial Uncle.
وقتل العم الإمبراطوري القديم.
Come with us to the magistrate's office.
تعالوا معنا إلى مكتب القاضي.
That's not right!
هذا ليس صحيحا!
You must be mistaken.
لابد أنك مخطئ.
I didn't kill anyone.
لم أقتل أحدا.
It wasn't me!
لم أكن أنا!
How could it not be you?
كيف لا تكون أنت؟
Last night at the Imperial Uncle's mansion,
الليلة الماضية في قصر العم الإمبراطوري،
you were the only guest invited.
لقد كنت الضيف الوحيد المدعو.
Besides,
بجانب،
I saw with my own eyes
لقد رأيت بأم عيني
that it was you.
أنك كنت أنت.
He's talking nonsense!
إنه يتكلم هراء!
The Imperial Uncle and I were close friends despite our age difference.
كان العم الإمبراطور وأنا صديقين مقربين على الرغم من فارق السن بيننا.
Everyone in the city knows this.
الجميع في المدينة يعرفون هذا.
How could I possibly harm the old man?
كيف يمكنني أن أؤذي الرجل العجوز؟
I'm being framed!
لقد تم تأطيري!
Who framed you?
من الذي أوقعك في الفخ؟
It's
إنه
the vegetable delivery couple temporarily hired by the estate.
الزوجان اللذان يقومان بتوصيل الخضروات واللذان تم تعيينهما مؤقتًا من قبل العقار.
They're the only ones with unknown backgrounds there.
إنهم الوحيدون الذين لديهم خلفيات غير معروفة هناك.
The day before yesterday,
أول أمس،
I heard them speaking disrespectfully about the Imperial Uncle,
سمعتهم يتحدثون بطريقة غير محترمة عن العم الإمبراطوري،
so I reprimanded them.
لذلك وبختهم.
I believe
انا أؤمن
they harbored resentment,
لقد كانوا يحملون الاستياء،
killed the Imperial Uncle,
قتل العم الإمبراطوري،
and framed me for it.
وأحاطوني به.
Outside the gate last night,
خارج البوابة الليلة الماضية،
there were indeed a young man and woman
وكان هناك بالفعل شاب وفتاة
who insisted on breaking into the Imperial Uncle's mansion.
الذين أصرّوا على اقتحام قصر العم الإمبراطوري.
They even claimed
حتى أنهم زعموا
the Imperial Uncle was in danger
كان العم الإمبراطوري في خطر
and injured many of our men.
وأصاب العديد من رجالنا.
Could they have escaped?
هل كان بإمكانهم الهروب؟
But even so,
ولكن مع ذلك،
as long as they can't be found,
طالما لم يتم العثور عليهم،
there's no evidence against them.
لا يوجد أي دليل ضدهم.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Where are these two people now?
أين هذين الشخصين الآن؟
Right here.
هنا.
The Imperial Uncle and the troupe leader
العم الإمبراطوري وقائد الفرقة
were indeed killed by Mei Jiulang,
لقد قُتلوا بالفعل على يد مي جيولانغ،
but not by the Mei Jiulang standing before you.
ولكن ليس من خلال مي جيولانغ الذي يقف أمامك.
Su Huasheng,
سو هوا شنج،
the show is over.
لقد انتهى العرض.
Time to be yourself again.
حان الوقت لتكون نفسك مرة أخرى.
How is this possible?
كيف هذا ممكن؟
He clearly died right here.
من الواضح أنه مات هنا.
Look!
ينظر!
Why is the door moving?
لماذا يتحرك الباب؟
What's happening?
ماذا يحدث؟
This is where Mei Jiulang
هذا هو المكان الذي يوجد فيه مي جيولانغ
brought us last night.
أحضرنا الليلة الماضية.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Don't you want to become a star at Ruichun Garden?
ألا تريد أن تصبح نجمًا في حديقة رويتشون؟
This place
هذا المكان
is where they really train the lead performers.
هذا هو المكان الذي يقومون فيه فعليًا بتدريب المؤدين الرائدين.
The manager of Ruichun Garden
مدير حديقة رويتشون
has been secretly
لقد كان سرا
doing unspeakable things.
القيام بأشياء لا توصف.
Every performer who becomes famous
كل فنان يصبح مشهورا
must train here
يجب التدريب هنا
to entertain the nobles.
لتسلية النبلاء.
Royal Uncle.
العم الملكي.
Jiulang.
جيولانغ.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Royal Uncle.
العم الملكي.
Did you get lost?
هل ضللت طريقك؟
Oh, indeed I did.
أوه، لقد فعلت ذلك بالفعل.
I was planning to visit
كنت أخطط للزيارة
Jiulang.
جيولانغ.
But when I reached this back garden,
ولكن عندما وصلت إلى هذه الحديقة الخلفية،
I saw
لقد رأيت
all these beautiful flowers in full bloom.
كل هذه الزهور الجميلة تتفتح بالكامل.
I was completely captivated.
لقد كنت مفتونًا تمامًا.
Those who know
الذين يعرفون
say the Queen's brother has refined taste.
يقال أن شقيق الملكة لديه ذوق رفيع.
Those who don't know
الذين لا يعرفون
might think any common flower
قد يعتقد البعض أن أي زهرة شائعة
could catch your eye, my lord.
قد يلفت انتباهك يا سيدي.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
In my opinion,
في رأيي،
among all these beauties,
بين كل هذه الجمالات،
our Jiulang is still the most radiant.
لا يزال جيولانغ الخاص بنا هو الأكثر إشراقًا.
In the front hall,
في القاعة الأمامية،
your household staff have been frantically looking for you.
لقد كان موظفو منزلك يبحثون عنك بشكل محموم.
Would you like
هل ترغب في ذلك؟
to make an appearance?
للظهور؟
Very well.
جيد جدا.
I'm just
انا فقط
waiting for Jiulang's performance
في انتظار أداء جيولانغ
to begin.
للبدء.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
The Empress's brother
شقيق الإمبراطورة
is so noble.
إنه نبيل للغاية.
How could someone as lowly as you
كيف يمكن لشخص متواضع مثلك أن يفعل ذلك؟
ever catch his eye?
هل لفت انتباهه من قبل؟
Huasheng.
هوا شينج.
Leave this place
أترك هذا المكان
and never come back.
ولا تعود أبدًا.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
You must be lying to me.
لا بد أنك تكذب علي.
He's nothing but a sadistic brute.
إنه ليس سوى وحش سادي.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
This is the whole truth.
هذه هي الحقيقة كاملة.
You are not Mei Jiulang after all.
أنت لست مي جيولانغ بعد كل شيء.
Be yourself,
كن نفسك،
Su Huasheng.
سو هوا شنج.
He's definitely not Boss Mei.
إنه بالتأكيد ليس الرئيس مي.
I thought Boss Mei was acting strange.
اعتقدت أن الرئيس مي كان يتصرف بغرابة.
My dear brother Huasheng,
أخي العزيز هوا شنغ،
may this letter bring you joy.
أتمنى أن تجلب لك هذه الرسالة السعادة.
In the past, I, Jiulang, was too shy
في الماضي، أنا، جيولانغ، كنت خجولًا جدًا
to reveal my true feelings to you.
لأكشف لك مشاعري الحقيقية.
Now that we must part ways,
الآن يجب علينا أن نفترق،
I entrust to this letter
أعهد إلى هذه الرسالة
the depth of my friendship.
عمق صداقتي.
When I was six years old,
عندما كنت في السادسة من عمري،
Chen Changqing saved me during a famine.
لقد أنقذني تشين تشانغتشينغ أثناء المجاعة.
What do you want, kid?
ماذا تريد يا صغيري؟
Please give me something to eat.
من فضلك أعطني شيئا لأكله.
No way, get out.
لا سبيل للخروج.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Please, I'm begging you.
من فضلك، أنا أتوسل إليك.
Just give me some food.
فقط أعطني بعض الطعام.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Little beggar.
متسول صغير.
You have a good voice.
لديك صوت جيد.
Would you like to come with me to learn opera?
هل ترغب في المجيء معي لتعلم الأوبرا؟
I promise you'll have enough to eat every day.
أعدك أنك سوف تأكل ما يكفي كل يوم.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
If you master it,
إذا أتقنته،
you can enjoy the finest food and drink every day.
يمكنك الاستمتاع بأشهى المأكولات والمشروبات كل يوم.
How about it?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
Jiulang practiced diligently.
تدرب جيولانغ بجد.
Everyone only saw Jiulang's glory on stage,
لم يشاهد الجميع مجد جيولانغ إلا على المسرح،
unaware of the filth beneath the costume.
غير مدرك للأوساخ الموجودة تحت الزي.
Jiulang.
جيولانغ.
Meet at the usual place.
اللقاء في المكان المعتاد.
Fame and fortune are not easily gained.
الشهرة والثروة ليس من السهل الحصول عليهما.
With gain comes misfortune.
مع الربح يأتي الشقاء.
In the darkness,
في الظلام،
Wealthy merchants and high officials
التجار الأثرياء وكبار المسؤولين
all treat me like a beast.
الجميع يعاملونني كوحش.
For years now,
منذ سنوات الآن،
Jiulang's art and beauty fade,
يتلاشى الفن والجمال في جيولانغ،
yet nobles and officials pursue him even more eagerly.
ومع ذلك فإن النبلاء والمسؤولين يلاحقونه بشغف أكبر.
You and I, from the same school,
أنت وأنا من نفس المدرسة
are birds in a cage.
طيور في قفص.
Only waiting to be abused.
في انتظار أن يتم إساءة معاملته فقط.
Huasheng, my brother,
هوا شنج، أخي،
though you have grand ambitions,
على الرغم من أن لديك طموحات كبيرة،
there are villains nearby
هناك أشرار في مكان قريب
who regard human life as worthless,
الذين يعتبرون الحياة البشرية لا قيمة لها،
I fear your wishes cannot be fulfilled.
أخشى أن رغباتك لن تتحقق.
Though I pretend to be harsh,
على الرغم من أنني أتظاهر بأنني قاسي،
I swear to protect you completely.
أقسم أني سأحميك بشكل كامل.
After today,
بعد اليوم،
mountains high and waters far,
الجبال العالية والمياه البعيدة،
do not look back.
لا تنظر للخلف
I can only lament
لا أستطيع إلا أن أحزن
that we will never be close again.
أننا لن نكون قريبين مرة أخرى.
I regret it and hate it.
أنا آسف وأكره ذلك.
If we meet again someday,
إذا التقينا مرة أخرى في يوم من الأيام،
I will surely share a drink with you
سأشاركك مشروبًا بالتأكيد
and face hardships together.
ويواجهون الصعوبات معًا.
Jiulang.
جيولانغ.
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
It's truly a joke.
إنها مزحة حقا.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
my jealousy was nothing but a joke.
لم تكن غيرتي سوى مزحة.
It was by my own hands
لقد كان بيدي
that I killed the person who loved me most.
أنني قتلت الشخص الذي أحبني أكثر من أي شخص آخر.
Senior Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
In my next life,
في حياتي القادمة،
I'll work like an ox and a horse
سأعمل مثل الثور والحصان
to repay my debt to you.
لسداد ديوني لك.
Huasheng.
هوا شينج.
Innkeeper.
صاحب النزل.
I had
لقد كان لدي
a very long dream.
حلم طويل جدًا.
It's my fault.
إنه خطئي.
I should have explained everything to you earlier.
كان ينبغي لي أن أشرح لك كل شيء في وقت سابق.
The person who really made the mistake
الشخص الذي ارتكب الخطأ حقا
has already been punished.
لقد تم معاقبته بالفعل.
Innkeeper.
صاحب النزل.
Innkeeper!
صاحب النزل!
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Madam Ling.
السيدة لينغ.
Innkeeper, what's going on?
صاحب النزل، ماذا يحدث؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Innkeeper!
صاحب النزل!